Wait.
Are you two also going to turn against me?
It's just a video.
A delay won't hurt.
Why all the fuss?
It's not about the video.
Then what is it?
Making a scene this early?
Zhou Yang,
Gu Chenyang might be transferring.
What?
He didn't even tell me.
I'm his childhood friend.
Now you know
why I'm mad.
And it's that Yudong.
Is it possible
he's not transferring,
just checking it out?
He's already got the jersey.
It's got the name
and number on it.
I took a picture.
You can see it clearly.
Don't get me wrong.
We really have finished eating.
Those who finally
reach the top of the pyramid
are often lonely.
Sometimes, you can only choose
between grades and friendship.
Here comes my idol.
Why do you suddenly invite me to play basketball?
Do I need a reason?
Let's have a match.
If I lose,
I'll treat you to water.
Water from my idol.
Thanks.
Nice.
You're not in good form today.
You lost to me.
Is it because of the transfer
to Yudong?
I heard they're also looking for you.
Many schools are.
I'm quite popular.
Have you decided where to go?
Not yet.
If it's about the best training,
the Institute of Physical Education
and Yudong are the top choices.
But I feel like something's missing.
What's missing?
I'm not sure how to explain it.
For example, your team,
although not a top-tier team,
has a great atmosphere.
You are very united.
You go together
to secretly spy on the enemy,
and go to the island to watch the meteor shower.
Good shot.
None of these are serious matters,
but they are very warm.
I think
this is team spirit.
Team spirit?
Yeah.
That's what's missing
at our school.
What do you think
if I transfer to Yibei?
Your school is so good.
Are you willing to leave?
That's true.
That's why I'm upset.
And you?
Are you going to transfer to a better team?
I...
I haven't decided yet.
You sound pretty sure
when you talk about me.
Maybe
that's because I'm an outsider.
Just like my dad.
Nice.
Gu Tingjun
won first prize
in this competition.
It's incredible.
Mom.
Come here.
Your dad is working overtime.
He won't be back until late.
You can take a break.
Mom,
what are you looking at?
These are all your dad's treasures.
Treasures?
When we got married,
he moved from his hometown to Yibei.
After all that sorting,
he only brought back this box of stuff.
It was his "dowry".
Impressive.
He was the first one
from his hometown
to get into a prestigious university.
When I knew him,
the whole school
called him a learning genius.
Later I found out
that his IQ wasn't actually higher than mine.
He just worked
many times harder than others,
to push himself to the limit,
which allowed him
to stay ahead.
Maybe he hoped I'd do the same.
That's how he succeeded.
He had no resources where he was born,
and no good fallback options.
So he had to rely on himself.
The life he has today,
for him,
is truly hard-won.
He's so strict with you
because he cares about you.
He hopes your future
will be smoother.
What's this?
This is
your dad's good buddy.
Good buddy?
Look, it's written on the back.
This was the reward
when he got
the top score in the city,
the school gave him this as a reward.
In his long years
of fighting alone,
he didn't have time to make friends.
This was his only companion,
and it was like his comrade-in-arms.
It's all broken.
Even so,
he still cherishes it.
So many certificates.
What competition is this?
This doll.
The one you sold at the charity auction.
Yes.
But back then,
wasn't it bought
by a young lady?
That lady was your dad's plant.
He knew
your charity auction venue was unreliable.
but you didn't care.
He wanted
to let you experience failure,
but in the end, he couldn't bear it,
so he had someone
buy the doll.
I'm going to take a shower.
If you're interested,
feel free to read more.
Okay.
[I've created a new group chat,]
without Gu Chenyang.
From now on,
you can send messages
in this new group.
Isn't this a bit over the top?
What if he's just looking into it,
not really planning to transfer?
I think Gu Chenyang
is probably being forced.
Since his dad
showed up at school,
I sensed something was off.
If he's forced,
why hide it from us?
Maybe he doesn't want us to worry.
Once it's resolved,
he'll tell us.
Gu Chenyang's calling.
Pick up.
Put it on speaker.
Need something from me?
Fu Binyan,
If I'm leaving Yibei,
can you take over the basketball team?
Are you really transferring to Yudong?
You
all know?
Actually, that day,
Qingyuan and I saw it.
You're going to Yudong
and even took their jersey.
We heard you calling Fu Binyan
last night.
Gu Chenyang,
do you even consider us friends?
Such a big deal,
and you didn't say a word?
I...
Gu Chenyang!
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
That's all you've got to say
after all this?
Lin Qingyuan!
You're the captain,
and you made a deal with the principal
to make it to the top eight!
You can't just walk away like this!
You brought our family
as a sponsor!
How am I supposed to
explain this to my parents?
What happened, Gu Chenyang?
Tell us.
We can help you.
Is it your dad?
Say something!
I...
I don't know how to say it.
But
the result is
I let you down.
Gu Chenyang,
do you know what this is called?
This is called betrayal!
Leave!
Leave now!
We won't talk to you anymore!
Go!
Leave!
Stop it, Lin Qingyuan.
Enough.
I'm sorry.
Go.
Gu Chenyang.
Are you really leaving?
If you leave,
you don't have to come back.
Do you want to
break up with me again?
Gu Chenyang.
I'm telling you,
if you leave, don't come back.
Gu Chenyang,
I transferred teams
for you.
I pulled strings
and risked my reputation.
All for you!
You won't know if you can go far
until you try.
With what?
Tell me, with what?
With your own future?
Take Yibei for example.
You're not a top-tier team,
but you have a great atmosphere
and unity.
That's what team spirit is.
Keep it up.
Yibei will win!
Those who reach
the top of the pyramid
are often lonely.
[Achievement and friendship,]
[often you can only choose one.]
[He's so strict with you,]
[probably because he cares about you.]
[He hopes your future will be smoother.]
We hope
Yibei Basketball Club
can make it to the provincial top eight.
I hope
Yibei Basketball Team
never disbands.
Thank you so much.
Okay, okay.
Bye.
Dad,
you're back just in time.
Coach Cheng just called.
The final interview
is next Saturday in Yudong.
Okay,
I'll be there.
Good.
I'll go back to my room.
Next Saturday
is the first knockout tournament.
Cheer up!
Come on!
Coach,
do you have any ideas about
the substitute for Gu Chenyang?
I'll think about it.
Look at the data here.
Actually, it should be adjusted here.
No need.
I've thought about the details here.
This is our class's
Reading Week report.
Senior Haoyu,
is this really okay?
Don't be so modest.
You clearly can do it.
Let's go, stop looking.